You hear about that
clusterfuck up on North Pine?
Dutch Stevens' kid.
How the fuck do you flip
a two-ton snow plow?
With stupidity.
The apple don't fall far from the gutter.
Well, that's kind of you.
On the house.
Thank you.
Hey, Rose.
You want a refill?
You can top me off anytime.
I like the new do.
Très chic.
Harmony Cobel.
Well, flip my toboggan.
You want coffee?
No.
Tables are for paying customers.
Fine. Then buy me a coffee.
The town is older than I remember.
Frailer.
Yeah, well, with the market readjustment
from a few years ago
and the fluctuating interest rates,
there was a retrenchment from some
of the core infrastructure investments.
I need a favor.
But not here.
Meet me at the factory.
- Hey, Dot. Close up for me.
- Sure.
You know how fucked it is
to ask me to come here?
I need you to drive me to Sissy's.
No, thanks.
If they're watching the house,
they'll recognize my car.
How much trouble are you in?
Enough.
You know she still lives by the nine?
I assumed.
Then you know she's a fucking pariah here.
You can stay in the truck.
I need to get something.
Why would I help you with anything?
We were once chums.
Old colleagues lift each other up.
Colleagues?
Child fucking labor.
Kier and Imogene met at the Ether Mill,
you know that?
Was she hacking up a lung at the time?
I can smell it on your breath.
Pathetic.
Fuck you.
You can help me or not.
But I'll not be the punching dummy
for your resentments.
Coast is clear.
You're higher than a bearded vulture.
Tell her to drop dead for me.
You are not welcome here.
This is trespass.
I have a mind to call the authorities.
I do not want that huff peddler
on my property.
You gave him his thirst for it.
You've a liar's mouth.
Do you want to come down here
and tell me what this is all about?
What have you done with my things?
Sold. To the poor.
They weren't yours to sell.
I sit in this house.
You do not.
Has anyone been here?
No one comes here.
Or telephoned?
A Mr. Drummond.
And what did he want?
What have you done, little mouse?
Harmony!
I want the key to Mother's room.
That room stays shut
until all who remember her sit with Kier.
You know this.
Give me the key.
Why do you bring nothing but woe
into my life?
No, it is you who cursed this house
with woe.
I will not have this quarrel.
What were her last words?
Child, do not test me.
What were they?
She said nothing after you pulled the tube
from her gullet.
There was gratitude in her eyes
to be freed from her suffering.
If only she had been a believer.
Perhaps she would have found solace
in the nine.
You didn't have to listen to her wheezing
as I did, day after day.
I would have cared for her myself,
had I not been at school.
Where you belonged.
I didn't even get to say goodbye.
Your studies were more important.
Mr. Eagan saw Kier in you.
He really did.
And the Wintertide Fellowship--
Even at the factory, no apprentice
was more industrious than you.
Such a disappointment you've proven to be.
What did Drummond tell you?
Return and plead forgiveness, child.
The Eagans will grant it.
And show me mercy,
just like you did with Mother.
Where is the key?
All you will find in there is pain.
Where is it?
I found it!
Come on.
Don't! Stand away!
Get your harpy hands off me.
You've no salutation here,
you blighted snuff slave.
All right, I missed you too.
You smell like crow skin.
I'll phone somebody. I swear it!
Yeah, call everyone.
We'll have a fucking kegger.
This is a pure house.
Back off or I'll put you in the bay!
What is it? What happened?
Nothing. Came to get you.
She's not too happy about it.
Did you see something?
No, but it's cold as shit in the truck,
and I gotta get back.
I have to find it.
Find what?
Just give me a minute just to think.
I liked her.
You barely knew her.
She hated Lumon more than I did.
That's all I needed to know.
At least she doesn't have to live
with Sissy anymore.
You wanna get high?
Wow.
I haven't done that since I was eight.
You ready to man the vat for ten hours?
It's so shameful that you sell it.
I don't think it's here.
What you're looking for.
Get out of here!
She wouldn't throw it away.
Find it?
Get the truck ready. And watch my head.
I'm going. Don't tell them I was here.
I would never bear falsity
to a steward of the Eagans.
Lumon destroyed this town.
You owe them no loyalty.
There was no town before the factory.
And what about your own employ?
Everything that you have,
you owe back to the Eagans as fealty.
Fealty?
Mine!
My designs!
Circuit blueprint...
Base code...
Overtime contingency...
Glasgow block. All of it.
Jame Eagan was the inventor.
So I've heard.
Extraordinary.
Why have you never spoken of this?
It was told Kier's knowledge is for all.
That is true.
That if I sought credit,
I would be banished.
I hope you die as painfully as she did.
It was her hand that removed the tube,
not mine.
No!
Your mother was a coward.
More sick in the soul than in the body.
Filled with malice and resentment.
I don't believe you!
I thought you were different...
my flower.
I tried to help you grow.
But now I see you are a weed,
just as she was.
Hey! Someone's comin'!
You better get going.
Hampton.
I'll see you around.
Come and tame these tempers, assholes.
Mrs. Selvig? Thank fuck,
I've been trying to reach you.
Yes, I'm aware.
So, listen, Mark has been reintegrating.
Reghabi?
Yeah.
And she hasn't killed him yet?
No. I mean, I think he's okay?
But listen, we wanna try something else.
Is Mark with you?
- Uh-huh. Yes.
- Put him on.
Yeah. Hello?
Tell me everything.